<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://houtube.eu.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://houtube.eu.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-10-31T17:18:41+03:00</updated>
<id>https://houtube.eu.org/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Houtube</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Robredo blasts call for revolutionary government: ‘Ang laking kalokohan’</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/robredo-blasts-call-for-revolutionary-government-ang-laking-kalokohan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Robredo blasts call for revolutionary government: ‘Ang laking kalokohan’" />
  <published>2020-09-01T16:09:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T16:09:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/robredo-blasts-call-for-revolutionary-government-ang-laking-kalokohan</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/robredo-blasts-call-for-revolutionary-government-ang-laking-kalokohan.html">&lt;p&gt;Calls to declare a revolutionary government are revived through an assembly on August 22. Vice President Leni Robredo calls it a ‘big joke,’ reiterating frustration at focusing on political matters instead of putting all efforts into the COVID-19 response.  &lt;br /&gt;Read:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Calls to declare a revolutionary government are revived through an assembly on August 22. Vice President Leni Robredo calls it a ‘big joke,’ reiterating frustration at focusing on political matters instead of putting all efforts into the COVID-19 response. Read:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ5m_1VG_hNzljo0Q/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ5m_1VG_hNzljo0Q/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Regret (Official Video) _ Ammy Virk _ Gold Boy _ Simar doraha latest punjabi songs 2020</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/regret-official-video-ammy-virk-gold-boy-simar-doraha-latest-punjabi-s.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Regret (Official Video) _ Ammy Virk _ Gold Boy _ Simar doraha latest punjabi songs 2020" />
  <published>2020-09-01T16:09:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T16:09:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/regret-official-video-ammy-virk-gold-boy-simar-doraha-latest-punjabi-s</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/regret-official-video-ammy-virk-gold-boy-simar-doraha-latest-punjabi-s.html">&lt;p&gt;REGRET LYRICS – AMMY VIRK  &lt;br /&gt;Dukhi te rehni aan  &lt;br /&gt;Par end nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Dukhi te rehni aan  &lt;br /&gt;Par end nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Mainu lagda hunn tainu bojh jehi  &lt;br /&gt;Apni yaari lagdi aa  &lt;br /&gt;Ta hi tainu meri sehat pehlan ton  &lt;br /&gt;Bhari lagdi aa bhari lagdi aa  &lt;br /&gt;Par hove pyar jithe aa  &lt;br /&gt;Look depend nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Dukhi te rehni aan  &lt;br /&gt;Par end nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Main tainu aive na peen diyan  &lt;br /&gt;Kasman paundi rahi  &lt;br /&gt;Dooje passe oh chandri  &lt;br /&gt;Bhar bhar peg paundi rahi  &lt;br /&gt;Main tainu aive na peen diyan  &lt;br /&gt;Kasman paundi rahi  &lt;br /&gt;Dooje passe oh chandri  &lt;br /&gt;Bhar bhar peg paundi rahi  &lt;br /&gt;Main kinne paath kare  &lt;br /&gt;Ne tainu paun layi  &lt;br /&gt;Ho kapde paunde rahi chhote  &lt;br /&gt;Tainu apnaun layi  &lt;br /&gt;Tainu apnaun layi  &lt;br /&gt;Shak aadat kudiyan di  &lt;br /&gt;Main tainu offend nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Dukhi te rehni aan  &lt;br /&gt;Par end nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Hunn aive pachhtawan  &lt;br /&gt;Tere naal kyun phas baithi  &lt;br /&gt;Simar main apne pyar baare  &lt;br /&gt;Mummy nu dass baithi  &lt;br /&gt;Hunn aive pachhtawan  &lt;br /&gt;Tere naal kyun phas baithi  &lt;br /&gt;Simar main apne pyar baare  &lt;br /&gt;Mummy nu dass baithi  &lt;br /&gt;Tera mood sad jeha hove  &lt;br /&gt;Ho mainu tokde rehnde ne  &lt;br /&gt;Mainu gharon baahr jaane to vi  &lt;br /&gt;Hunn rokde rehnde ne  &lt;br /&gt;Haan rokde rehnde ne  &lt;br /&gt;Tu taan jhat keh dena  &lt;br /&gt;Main time spend nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Dukhi te rehni aan  &lt;br /&gt;Par end nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Ek text type ta kardi aan  &lt;br /&gt;Main send nai kardi  &lt;br /&gt;Regret Song Detail  &lt;br /&gt;Lyrics by: Simar Doraha  &lt;br /&gt;Singer: Ammy Virk  &lt;br /&gt;Composer: Goldboy&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="music" />
  <summary type="html">REGRET LYRICS – AMMY VIRK Dukhi te rehni aan Par end nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Dukhi te rehni aan Par end nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Mainu lagda hunn tainu bojh jehi Apni yaari lagdi aa Ta hi tainu meri sehat pehlan ton Bhari lagdi aa bhari lagdi aa Par hove pyar jithe aa Look depend nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Dukhi te rehni aan Par end nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Main tainu aive na peen diyan Kasman paundi rahi Dooje passe oh chandri Bhar bhar peg paundi rahi Main tainu aive na peen diyan Kasman paundi rahi Dooje passe oh chandri Bhar bhar peg paundi rahi Main kinne paath kare Ne tainu paun layi Ho kapde paunde rahi chhote Tainu apnaun layi Tainu apnaun layi Shak aadat kudiyan di Main tainu offend nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Dukhi te rehni aan Par end nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Hunn aive pachhtawan Tere naal kyun phas baithi Simar main apne pyar baare Mummy nu dass baithi Hunn aive pachhtawan Tere naal kyun phas baithi Simar main apne pyar baare Mummy nu dass baithi Tera mood sad jeha hove Ho mainu tokde rehnde ne Mainu gharon baahr jaane to vi Hunn rokde rehnde ne Haan rokde rehnde ne Tu taan jhat keh dena Main time spend nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Dukhi te rehni aan Par end nai kardi Ek text type ta kardi aan Main send nai kardi Regret Song Detail Lyrics by: Simar Doraha Singer: Ammy Virk Composer: Goldboy</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ8p51VH8xU1z_Wi8/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ8p51VH8xU1z_Wi8/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Les chiffres trompeurs de la violence en France 26 08 2020 Désintox ARTE</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/les-chiffres-trompeurs-de-la-violence-en-france-26-08-2020-d-sintox-ar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Les chiffres trompeurs de la violence en France 26 08 2020 Désintox ARTE" />
  <published>2020-09-01T16:07:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T16:07:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/les-chiffres-trompeurs-de-la-violence-en-france-26-08-2020-d-sintox-ar</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/les-chiffres-trompeurs-de-la-violence-en-france-26-08-2020-d-sintox-ar.html">&lt;p&gt;Retrouvez Désintox du lundi au jeudi, dans l’émission 28 minutes, à 20h sur Arte.  &lt;br /&gt;Sur Facebook  :   &lt;br /&gt;Sur YouTube :   &lt;br /&gt;Sur instagram :   &lt;br /&gt;Sur le site d’Arte :   &lt;br /&gt;La France est-elle plus violente qu’il y a trente ans ? Ce débat récurrent s’est à nouveau invité dans l’actualité, après la parution d’un dossier dans le Figaro, compilant trois jours de crimes et délits en France. &quot;Ensauvagement de la société&quot;, a même diagnostiqué Gérald Darmanin, ministre de l’Intérieur. Sur les réseaux sociaux, le sujet a été l’occasion d’un vif échange entre le sociologue Laurent Mucchielli, affirmant que la violence était stable depuis 20 ou 30 ans en France, et le cofondateur du Printemps Républicain, Gilles Clavreul, jurant le contraire, graphiques à l’appui.   &lt;br /&gt;Les uns montrent une multiplication par 4 du nombre de victimes de faits violents, entre 1975 et 2000. D’autres autres indiquent une hausse de 25% des coups et blessures volontaires au cours des 10 dernières années. Ces chiffres correspondent aux faits constatés par les forces de l’ordre. Mais cela fait des années que tous les spécialistes s’accordent sur le fait que ces statistiques reflètent, plus que la délinquance réelle, les changements de méthode d’enregistrement des forces de l’ordre ou encore la propension des victimes à porter plainte. Et qu’elles fluctuent en fonction des réformes de la loi..   &lt;br /&gt;Pour étudier l’évolution de la délinquance sur le temps long, il faut plutôt regarder les enquêtes de « victimation », où on demande à des échantillons représentatifs de la population s’ils ont subi des violences. Ces enquêtes existent depuis une grosse vingtaine d’années en France. Elles possèdent, elles aussi, des limites, parce que la manière de poser des questions a pu parfois évoluer dans le temps. Toutefois, elles indiquent, sur les 10 ou 20 dernières années, que la part de la population se disant victime de violences est relativement stable. Ni à la hausse, ni à la baisse, donc.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Retrouvez Désintox du lundi au jeudi, dans l’émission 28 minutes, à 20h sur Arte. Sur Facebook : Sur YouTube : Sur instagram : Sur le site d’Arte : La France est-elle plus violente qu’il y a trente ans ? Ce débat récurrent s’est à nouveau invité dans l’actualité, après la parution d’un dossier dans le Figaro, compilant trois jours de crimes et délits en France. &quot;Ensauvagement de la société&quot;, a même diagnostiqué Gérald Darmanin, ministre de l’Intérieur. Sur les réseaux sociaux, le sujet a été l’occasion d’un vif échange entre le sociologue Laurent Mucchielli, affirmant que la violence était stable depuis 20 ou 30 ans en France, et le cofondateur du Printemps Républicain, Gilles Clavreul, jurant le contraire, graphiques à l’appui. Les uns montrent une multiplication par 4 du nombre de victimes de faits violents, entre 1975 et 2000. D’autres autres indiquent une hausse de 25% des coups et blessures volontaires au cours des 10 dernières années. Ces chiffres correspondent aux faits constatés par les forces de l’ordre. Mais cela fait des années que tous les spécialistes s’accordent sur le fait que ces statistiques reflètent, plus que la délinquance réelle, les changements de méthode d’enregistrement des forces de l’ordre ou encore la propension des victimes à porter plainte. Et qu’elles fluctuent en fonction des réformes de la loi.. Pour étudier l’évolution de la délinquance sur le temps long, il faut plutôt regarder les enquêtes de « victimation », où on demande à des échantillons représentatifs de la population s’ils ont subi des violences. Ces enquêtes existent depuis une grosse vingtaine d’années en France. Elles possèdent, elles aussi, des limites, parce que la manière de poser des questions a pu parfois évoluer dans le temps. Toutefois, elles indiquent, sur les 10 ou 20 dernières années, que la part de la population se disant victime de violences est relativement stable. Ni à la hausse, ni à la baisse, donc.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQL_B1VHkZYAU0SHG/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQL_B1VHkZYAU0SHG/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/feelings-remix-ringtone-sumit-goswami-new-song.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song" />
  <published>2020-09-01T16:05:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T16:05:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/feelings-remix-ringtone-sumit-goswami-new-song</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/feelings-remix-ringtone-sumit-goswami-new-song.html">&lt;p&gt;#feelings_ringtone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="music" />
  <summary type="html">#feelings_ringtoneFeelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song Feelings Remix Ringtone Sumit Goswami New Song</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBUw1VHp-LGUiSlo/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBUw1VHp-LGUiSlo/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/gazidis-we-want-to-strengthen-as-a-team-and-club.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’" />
  <published>2020-09-01T16:00:21+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T16:00:21+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/gazidis-we-want-to-strengthen-as-a-team-and-club</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/gazidis-we-want-to-strengthen-as-a-team-and-club.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Gazidis: 'We want to strengthen as a team and Club'&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’ Gazidis: ‘We want to strengthen as a team and Club’ Gazidis: 'We want to strengthen as a team and Club'</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQDah1VHOKFgKhPBr/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQDah1VHOKFgKhPBr/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Deretan Jenderal Polisi yang Tersandung Kasus Korupsi</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/deretan-jenderal-polisi-yang-tersandung-kasus-korupsi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deretan Jenderal Polisi yang Tersandung Kasus Korupsi" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:54:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:54:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/deretan-jenderal-polisi-yang-tersandung-kasus-korupsi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/deretan-jenderal-polisi-yang-tersandung-kasus-korupsi.html">&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, KOMPAS.TV - Keterlibatan jenderal polisi dalam kasus surat jalan dan penghapusan red notice Djoko Tjandra bukanlah yang pertama. Kompas mencatat, dalam 14 tahun terakhir, setidaknya ada 4 kasus korupsi yang melibatkan jenderal polisi.   &lt;br /&gt;Di tahun 2006 lalu nama mantan Kabareskrim Polri Komjen Pol Purnawirawan Suyitno Landung dan mantan Direktur II Ekonomi Khusus Bareskrim Polri Brigjen Pol Purnawirawan Samuel Ismoko, menjadi perhatian publik. Keduanya diketahui menerima suap dalam penanganan kasus pembobolan bank bni yang dilakukan Maria Pauline Lumowa dan Adrian Waworuntu.   &lt;br /&gt;Tahun 2011 dua nama jenderal polisi kembali menjadi perhatian publik karena terlibat dalam makelar kasus mafia pajak Gayus Tambunan. Mereka adalah Irjen Pol Raja Erizman dan Brigjen Pol Edmon Ilyas. Keduanya merupakan mantan Direktur II Ekonomi Khusus Bareskrim yang menangani kasus mantan pegawai pajak Gayus Tambunan.    &lt;br /&gt;Saat itu, publik dihebohkan dengan pemberitaan kasus korupsi pengadaan simulator SIM senilai Rp 198 miliar. Mantan Kakorlantas Polri Irjen Pol Djoko Susilo dan mantan Wakil Kakorlantas Brigjen Pol Didik Purnomo harus bertanggung jawab terkait kasus ini.   &lt;br /&gt;Djoko Susilo divonis 18 tahun penjara, disita seluruh kekayaannya dan dicabut hak politiknya. Sementara Didik Purnomo divonis 5 tahun penjara karena dinilai terbukti bersalah dalam kasus ini.   &lt;br /&gt;Kini kita kembali mendengar nama tiga jenderal polisi dalam pusaran drama Djoko Tjandra, terpidana kasus cessie Bank Bali. Sebelum ditangkap di Malaysia 30 Juli lalu, Djoko Tjandra diketahui sempat bebas keluar masuk Indonesia tanpa terdeteksi pada bulan Juni 2020.    &lt;br /&gt;Bebasnya djoko tjandra berkeliaran di indonesia pada bulan juni lalu ditengarai berkat bantuan Brigjen Pol Prasetijo Utomo, Brigjen Nugroho Slamet Wibowo dan Irjen Napoleon Bonaparte.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">JAKARTA, KOMPAS.TV - Keterlibatan jenderal polisi dalam kasus surat jalan dan penghapusan red notice Djoko Tjandra bukanlah yang pertama. Kompas mencatat, dalam 14 tahun terakhir, setidaknya ada 4 kasus korupsi yang melibatkan jenderal polisi. Di tahun 2006 lalu nama mantan Kabareskrim Polri Komjen Pol Purnawirawan Suyitno Landung dan mantan Direktur II Ekonomi Khusus Bareskrim Polri Brigjen Pol Purnawirawan Samuel Ismoko, menjadi perhatian publik. Keduanya diketahui menerima suap dalam penanganan kasus pembobolan bank bni yang dilakukan Maria Pauline Lumowa dan Adrian Waworuntu. Tahun 2011 dua nama jenderal polisi kembali menjadi perhatian publik karena terlibat dalam makelar kasus mafia pajak Gayus Tambunan. Mereka adalah Irjen Pol Raja Erizman dan Brigjen Pol Edmon Ilyas. Keduanya merupakan mantan Direktur II Ekonomi Khusus Bareskrim yang menangani kasus mantan pegawai pajak Gayus Tambunan. Saat itu, publik dihebohkan dengan pemberitaan kasus korupsi pengadaan simulator SIM senilai Rp 198 miliar. Mantan Kakorlantas Polri Irjen Pol Djoko Susilo dan mantan Wakil Kakorlantas Brigjen Pol Didik Purnomo harus bertanggung jawab terkait kasus ini. Djoko Susilo divonis 18 tahun penjara, disita seluruh kekayaannya dan dicabut hak politiknya. Sementara Didik Purnomo divonis 5 tahun penjara karena dinilai terbukti bersalah dalam kasus ini. Kini kita kembali mendengar nama tiga jenderal polisi dalam pusaran drama Djoko Tjandra, terpidana kasus cessie Bank Bali. Sebelum ditangkap di Malaysia 30 Juli lalu, Djoko Tjandra diketahui sempat bebas keluar masuk Indonesia tanpa terdeteksi pada bulan Juni 2020. Bebasnya djoko tjandra berkeliaran di indonesia pada bulan juni lalu ditengarai berkat bantuan Brigjen Pol Prasetijo Utomo, Brigjen Nugroho Slamet Wibowo dan Irjen Napoleon Bonaparte.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQkXs1VIny6R1RDFe/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQkXs1VIny6R1RDFe/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">India-China Faceoff : Chinese Foreign Minister बोले,बातचीत से सुलझाएंगे विवाद वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/india-china-faceoff-chinese-foreign-minister.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India-China Faceoff : Chinese Foreign Minister बोले,बातचीत से सुलझाएंगे विवाद वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:52:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:52:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/india-china-faceoff-chinese-foreign-minister</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/india-china-faceoff-chinese-foreign-minister.html">&lt;p&gt;China continues to manipulate the Line of Actual Control (LAC). On the one hand, China tried to infiltrate, which was thwarted by the Indian Army, on the other hand, China has been singing peace on the globe. China’s attitude seems to have changed after receiving a befitting reply from the Indian Army on the night of 29-30 August in the Pangong Tso Lake area of ​​Ladakh. Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi has said that we want a good relationship with India and the two countries will resolve all disputes through mutual negotiations.   &lt;br /&gt;लाइन ऑफ एक्चुअल कंट्रोल (एलएसी) पर चीन का चालबाजी जारी है. एक ओर चीन ने घुसपैठ की कोशिश की, जिसे भारतीय सेना ने नाकाम कर दिया, तो दूसरी ओर विश्वपटल पर चीन शांति का राग अलाप रहा है. लद्दाख के पैंगोंग त्सो झील इलाके  में 29-30 अगस्त की रात को भारतीय सेना से मुंहतोड़ जवाब मिलने के बाद चीन का रुख बदला-बदला नज़र आ रहा है. चीनी विदेश मंत्री वांग यी ने कहा है कि भारत के साथ हम अच्छे रिश्ते चाहते हैं और दोनों देश आपसी बातचीत से सभी विवादों को सुलझा लेंगे.   &lt;br /&gt;#IndiaChinaClash #IndianArmy #J20FighterJet&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">China continues to manipulate the Line of Actual Control (LAC). On the one hand, China tried to infiltrate, which was thwarted by the Indian Army, on the other hand, China has been singing peace on the globe. China’s attitude seems to have changed after receiving a befitting reply from the Indian Army on the night of 29-30 August in the Pangong Tso Lake area of ​​Ladakh. Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi has said that we want a good relationship with India and the two countries will resolve all disputes through mutual negotiations. लाइन ऑफ एक्चुअल कंट्रोल (एलएसी) पर चीन का चालबाजी जारी है. एक ओर चीन ने घुसपैठ की कोशिश की, जिसे भारतीय सेना ने नाकाम कर दिया, तो दूसरी ओर विश्वपटल पर चीन शांति का राग अलाप रहा है. लद्दाख के पैंगोंग त्सो झील इलाके में 29-30 अगस्त की रात को भारतीय सेना से मुंहतोड़ जवाब मिलने के बाद चीन का रुख बदला-बदला नज़र आ रहा है. चीनी विदेश मंत्री वांग यी ने कहा है कि भारत के साथ हम अच्छे रिश्ते चाहते हैं और दोनों देश आपसी बातचीत से सभी विवादों को सुलझा लेंगे. #IndiaChinaClash #IndianArmy #J20FighterJet</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQz7h1VJU8hr_7c3S/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQz7h1VJU8hr_7c3S/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Rhea Chakraborty और उनकी family के बारे में क्या सोचते हैं उनके पड़ोसी, ये मिला जवाब FilmiBeat</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/rhea-chakraborty-family-filmibeat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rhea Chakraborty और उनकी family के बारे में क्या सोचते हैं उनके पड़ोसी, ये मिला जवाब FilmiBeat" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:51:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:51:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/rhea-chakraborty-family-filmibeat</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/rhea-chakraborty-family-filmibeat.html">&lt;p&gt;Everyday new revelations coming out about Rhea Chakraborty, now her neighbours gives shocking statement on Rhea and her family.Watch Out   &lt;br /&gt;#SushantSinghRajput #RheaChakraborty&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">Everyday new revelations coming out about Rhea Chakraborty, now her neighbours gives shocking statement on Rhea and her family.Watch Out #SushantSinghRajput #RheaChakraborty</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQL4i1VHj7XjHzqEL/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQL4i1VHj7XjHzqEL/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/barbara-hepworth-s-sculpture-records-animating-the-archives.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:48:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:48:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/barbara-hepworth-s-sculpture-records-animating-the-archives</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/barbara-hepworth-s-sculpture-records-animating-the-archives.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives Barbara Hepworth’s Sculpture Records Animating the Archives</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQC861VHKOW94ZKLp/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQC861VHKOW94ZKLp/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Esenler’de maskeli 4 şüpheli 11 kilo altını gasp etti</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/esenler-de-maskeli-4-pheli-11-kilo-alt-n-gasp-etti.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Esenler’de maskeli 4 şüpheli 11 kilo altını gasp etti" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:47:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:47:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/esenler-de-maskeli-4-pheli-11-kilo-alt-n-gasp-etti</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/esenler-de-maskeli-4-pheli-11-kilo-alt-n-gasp-etti.html">&lt;p&gt;Esenler’de bir kuyumcu sabah saatlerinde evinden çıkıp iş yerine gideceği sırada gasp edildi. Kuyumcunun evinin önünde bekleyen 4 kişi 11 kilo altını çalarak kayıplara karıştı. Maskeli şüphelilerin silahlı gasp anı kameralara saniye saniye yansıdı.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Esenler’de bir kuyumcu sabah saatlerinde evinden çıkıp iş yerine gideceği sırada gasp edildi. Kuyumcunun evinin önünde bekleyen 4 kişi 11 kilo altını çalarak kayıplara karıştı. Maskeli şüphelilerin silahlı gasp anı kameralara saniye saniye yansıdı.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSBC1VHw5kmUDWkF/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSBC1VHw5kmUDWkF/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Boutchou Film</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/boutchou-film.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Boutchou Film" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:46:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:46:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/boutchou-film</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/boutchou-film.html">&lt;p&gt;Boutchou Film - Bande-annonce officielle - UGC Distribution - Synopsis: Paul et Virginie viennent d’avoir un petit garçon. Heureux de découvrir leur nouvelle vie de jeunes parents, ils n’imaginaient pas que leur Boutchou allait devenir l’enjeu d’une lutte sans merci entre les grand-parents…  &lt;br /&gt;Pour gagner l’exclusivité du petit adoré, grand-pères et grand-mères sont prêts à mettre en place tous les stratagèmes…  &lt;br /&gt;Au cinéma le 23 septembre.  &lt;br /&gt;Un film d’Adrien Piquet-Gauthier  &lt;br /&gt;Avec : Carole Bouquet, Gérard Darmon, Clémentine Célarié, Stéfi Celma et, Lannick Gautry&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Boutchou Film - Bande-annonce officielle - UGC Distribution - Synopsis: Paul et Virginie viennent d’avoir un petit garçon. Heureux de découvrir leur nouvelle vie de jeunes parents, ils n’imaginaient pas que leur Boutchou allait devenir l’enjeu d’une lutte sans merci entre les grand-parents… Pour gagner l’exclusivité du petit adoré, grand-pères et grand-mères sont prêts à mettre en place tous les stratagèmes… Au cinéma le 23 septembre. Un film d’Adrien Piquet-Gauthier Avec : Carole Bouquet, Gérard Darmon, Clémentine Célarié, Stéfi Celma et, Lannick Gautry</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPzPE1VJaACKcxx-X/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPzPE1VJaACKcxx-X/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Wolverines Spotted In Mount Rainier After 100-Year Absence</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/wolverines-spotted-in-mount-rainier-after-100-year-absence.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wolverines Spotted In Mount Rainier After 100-Year Absence" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:41:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:41:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/wolverines-spotted-in-mount-rainier-after-100-year-absence</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/wolverines-spotted-in-mount-rainier-after-100-year-absence.html">&lt;p&gt;Conservationists at Mount Rainier National Park in Washington State have something to celebrate.  &lt;br /&gt;Officials have spotted a wolverine mother and her two offspring, known as kits in the park.  &lt;br /&gt;A female of reproductive age and health hasn’t been seen in the park for over a century.  &lt;br /&gt;According to Gizmodo, the sighting suggests ecological conditions in the area are improving.  &lt;br /&gt;Wolverines, despite their popularity in the public’s imagination, are very rare in nature.  &lt;br /&gt;Only an estimated 300 to 1,000 wolverines are thought to exist in the Lower 48 states.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Conservationists at Mount Rainier National Park in Washington State have something to celebrate. Officials have spotted a wolverine mother and her two offspring, known as kits in the park. A female of reproductive age and health hasn’t been seen in the park for over a century. According to Gizmodo, the sighting suggests ecological conditions in the area are improving. Wolverines, despite their popularity in the public’s imagination, are very rare in nature. Only an estimated 300 to 1,000 wolverines are thought to exist in the Lower 48 states.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQdwQ1VIPqZQBilZF/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQdwQ1VIPqZQBilZF/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">BMW S 1000 XR Review First Ride</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/bmw-s-1000-xr-review-first-ride.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BMW S 1000 XR Review First Ride" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:39:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:39:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/bmw-s-1000-xr-review-first-ride</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/bmw-s-1000-xr-review-first-ride.html">&lt;p&gt;BMW placed its sensational inline-four superbike engine into a more upright and touring-focused package with its introductory 2015 S 1000 XR. Fast-forward and the Motorrad team applies the 2020 round of S 1000 RR technical updates to this liter-class XR. But where the superbike comes up short in areas, the XR stands out in its high-level refinement. This is a motorcycle that is adept at touring as it is bonzai sport riding…  &lt;br /&gt;Find out more:   &lt;br /&gt;Photography: Jeff Allen  &lt;br /&gt;Videography/edit: Bert Beltran&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tech" />
  <summary type="html">BMW placed its sensational inline-four superbike engine into a more upright and touring-focused package with its introductory 2015 S 1000 XR. Fast-forward and the Motorrad team applies the 2020 round of S 1000 RR technical updates to this liter-class XR. But where the superbike comes up short in areas, the XR stands out in its high-level refinement. This is a motorcycle that is adept at touring as it is bonzai sport riding… Find out more: Photography: Jeff Allen Videography/edit: Bert Beltran</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQwkM1VJN3wDtYwX_/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQwkM1VJN3wDtYwX_/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">For the first time in 40 years, Indian economy is in huge recession, says Rahul Gandhi</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/for-the-first-time-in-40-years-indian-economy-is-in-huge-recession-say.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For the first time in 40 years, Indian economy is in huge recession, says Rahul Gandhi" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:39:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:39:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/for-the-first-time-in-40-years-indian-economy-is-in-huge-recession-say</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/for-the-first-time-in-40-years-indian-economy-is-in-huge-recession-say.html">&lt;p&gt;The unfortunate truth of the economic tragedy that the country is facing will be confirmed today. For the first time in 40 years, the Indian economy is in a huge recession. The ‘non-satyagrahi’ are blaming God for this, tweeted Rahul Gandhi.  &lt;br /&gt;#RahulGandhi #Congress #BJP #Economy #NonSatyagrahi #Lockdown #GDP #PMModi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The unfortunate truth of the economic tragedy that the country is facing will be confirmed today. For the first time in 40 years, the Indian economy is in a huge recession. The ‘non-satyagrahi’ are blaming God for this, tweeted Rahul Gandhi. #RahulGandhi #Congress #BJP #Economy #NonSatyagrahi #Lockdown #GDP #PMModi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQqKA1VJDFvziBpQW/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQqKA1VJDFvziBpQW/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Jadi Tersangka Korupsi, Mantan Kepala BPN Bali Bunuh Diri di Toilet Kejaksaan</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/jadi-tersangka-korupsi-mantan-kepala-bpn-bali-bunuh-diri-di-toilet-kej.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jadi Tersangka Korupsi, Mantan Kepala BPN Bali Bunuh Diri di Toilet Kejaksaan" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:37:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:37:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/jadi-tersangka-korupsi-mantan-kepala-bpn-bali-bunuh-diri-di-toilet-kej</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/jadi-tersangka-korupsi-mantan-kepala-bpn-bali-bunuh-diri-di-toilet-kej.html">&lt;p&gt;KOMPAS.TV - Mantan Kepala Badan Pertanahan Nasional (BPN) Denpasar, Bali yakni TN (53), meninggal dunia seusai bunuh diri di toilet Kejaksaan Tinggi Bali, pada Senin (31/8/2020) malam.   &lt;br /&gt;TN nekat mengakhiri hidupnya, seusai diperiksa penyidik Kejati Bali, dan hendak ditahan di Lapas Kerobokan.  Dilansir oleh Kompas.com, hal itu disampaikan oleh Wakajati Bali, Asep Maryono.   &lt;br /&gt;&quot;Ketika perjalanan (ke mobil tahanan) itu dia izin ke toilet dan bunuh diri. Kami sudah dapat konfirmasi yang bersangkutan meninggal dunia,&quot; kata Maryono, di Kejati Bali, Senin (31/8/2020).    &lt;br /&gt;Maryono mengatakan, TN awalnya diperiksa Kejati Bali sejak pukul 10.00 Wita. Saat itu, TN membawa sebuah tas kecil dan diminta petugas untuk menyimpannya di loker sebelum diperiksa.    &lt;br /&gt;Kemudian saat jam makan siang, pemeriksaan sempat terhenti karena tersangka izin untuk makan dan sembahyang.  Namun hingga pukul 15.00 Wita, TN belum juga memperlihatkan diri dan tidak bisa dihubungi.   &lt;br /&gt;Kejati Bali lalu melacaknya, dan menemukan TN berada di rumahnya, di Gunung Talang, Denpasar. Ia lalu dijemput dan dibawa Kejati untuk dilanjutkan pemeriksaan yang berlangsung hingga pukul 19.00 Wita.    &lt;br /&gt;Setelah pemeriksaan, rencananya TN akan ditahan di Lapas Kerobokan. Kemudian sebelum turun ke lantai I, TN izin untuk pergi ke toilet.  Namun tak lama setelahnya, terdengar suara letusan senjata api.    &lt;br /&gt;Petugas yang mengawalnya lalu masuk ke toilet dan menemukan TN sudah terkapar.  TN lalu dilarikan ke rumah sakit dan dinyatakan meninggal dunia.    &lt;br /&gt;Dengan meninggalnya tersangka, maka kasus dugaan gratifikasi ini ditutup.    &lt;br /&gt;&quot;Pasca meninggalnya tentu kami tutup kasus karena. Kalau soal barang sitaan nanti akan ada prosesnya sendiri,&quot; kata dia.   &lt;br /&gt;Diberitakan sebelumnya, TN memanfaatkan jabatannya untuk mendapatkan keuntungan dalam beberapa penerbitan sertifikat tanah. TN ditetapkan sebagai tersangka gratifikasi pada 13 November dan 13 April 2020 sebagai tersangka Tindak Pidana Pencucian Uang.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">KOMPAS.TV - Mantan Kepala Badan Pertanahan Nasional (BPN) Denpasar, Bali yakni TN (53), meninggal dunia seusai bunuh diri di toilet Kejaksaan Tinggi Bali, pada Senin (31/8/2020) malam. TN nekat mengakhiri hidupnya, seusai diperiksa penyidik Kejati Bali, dan hendak ditahan di Lapas Kerobokan. Dilansir oleh Kompas.com, hal itu disampaikan oleh Wakajati Bali, Asep Maryono. &quot;Ketika perjalanan (ke mobil tahanan) itu dia izin ke toilet dan bunuh diri. Kami sudah dapat konfirmasi yang bersangkutan meninggal dunia,&quot; kata Maryono, di Kejati Bali, Senin (31/8/2020). Maryono mengatakan, TN awalnya diperiksa Kejati Bali sejak pukul 10.00 Wita. Saat itu, TN membawa sebuah tas kecil dan diminta petugas untuk menyimpannya di loker sebelum diperiksa. Kemudian saat jam makan siang, pemeriksaan sempat terhenti karena tersangka izin untuk makan dan sembahyang. Namun hingga pukul 15.00 Wita, TN belum juga memperlihatkan diri dan tidak bisa dihubungi. Kejati Bali lalu melacaknya, dan menemukan TN berada di rumahnya, di Gunung Talang, Denpasar. Ia lalu dijemput dan dibawa Kejati untuk dilanjutkan pemeriksaan yang berlangsung hingga pukul 19.00 Wita. Setelah pemeriksaan, rencananya TN akan ditahan di Lapas Kerobokan. Kemudian sebelum turun ke lantai I, TN izin untuk pergi ke toilet. Namun tak lama setelahnya, terdengar suara letusan senjata api. Petugas yang mengawalnya lalu masuk ke toilet dan menemukan TN sudah terkapar. TN lalu dilarikan ke rumah sakit dan dinyatakan meninggal dunia. Dengan meninggalnya tersangka, maka kasus dugaan gratifikasi ini ditutup. &quot;Pasca meninggalnya tentu kami tutup kasus karena. Kalau soal barang sitaan nanti akan ada prosesnya sendiri,&quot; kata dia. Diberitakan sebelumnya, TN memanfaatkan jabatannya untuk mendapatkan keuntungan dalam beberapa penerbitan sertifikat tanah. TN ditetapkan sebagai tersangka gratifikasi pada 13 November dan 13 April 2020 sebagai tersangka Tindak Pidana Pencucian Uang.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQzbV1VJUtDUlOkYd/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQzbV1VJUtDUlOkYd/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Amitabh Ko Film Coolie Ke Haadse Se Bachaya Ja Sakta tha</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/amitabh-ko-film-coolie-ke-haadse-se-bachaya-ja-sakta-tha.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amitabh Ko Film Coolie Ke Haadse Se Bachaya Ja Sakta tha" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:31:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:31:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/amitabh-ko-film-coolie-ke-haadse-se-bachaya-ja-sakta-tha</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/amitabh-ko-film-coolie-ke-haadse-se-bachaya-ja-sakta-tha.html">&lt;p&gt;#Bollywood #Bollywoodmunch #BollywoodNews #BollywoodGossip  &lt;br /&gt;Amitabh Ko Film Coolie Ke Haadse Se Bachaya Ja Sakta tha  &lt;br /&gt;Smita Patil had a dream that he was injured, with which Smita Patil called Amitabh Bachchan in the middle of the night and told him her dream and Amitabh laughed and said that I am fine Smita ji you don’t get upset. When Amitabh Bachchan went to shoot the film the next day, there was an accident on the film’s set. Let me tell you, during the shooting of ‘Coolie’ in the year 1982, Amitabh was badly injured.  &lt;br /&gt;Subscribe The Channel For More Updates -   &lt;br /&gt;Check out some of the Great Bollywood Updates From Bollywood Munch  &lt;br /&gt;Like * Comment * Share - Don’t forget to LIKE the video and write your COMMENT’s  &lt;br /&gt;Follow Us On   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook Page : -   &lt;br /&gt;Google+ :-   &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:-  &lt;br /&gt;Dailymotion :-   &lt;br /&gt;About Us :-   &lt;br /&gt;Bollywood Munch is the official Channel For Bollywood News, Gossips, Movie Reviews, Awards, Celebrities, Films, Events Updates and More. Bollywood Munch is Best Described as a Entertainment. Please Like and Share the page for all Latest Bollywood Updates. Thanks for you support and love.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">#Bollywood #Bollywoodmunch #BollywoodNews #BollywoodGossip Amitabh Ko Film Coolie Ke Haadse Se Bachaya Ja Sakta tha Smita Patil had a dream that he was injured, with which Smita Patil called Amitabh Bachchan in the middle of the night and told him her dream and Amitabh laughed and said that I am fine Smita ji you don’t get upset. When Amitabh Bachchan went to shoot the film the next day, there was an accident on the film’s set. Let me tell you, during the shooting of ‘Coolie’ in the year 1982, Amitabh was badly injured. Subscribe The Channel For More Updates - Check out some of the Great Bollywood Updates From Bollywood Munch Like * Comment * Share - Don’t forget to LIKE the video and write your COMMENT’s Follow Us On Facebook Page : - Google+ :- Twitter:- Dailymotion :- About Us :- Bollywood Munch is the official Channel For Bollywood News, Gossips, Movie Reviews, Awards, Celebrities, Films, Events Updates and More. Bollywood Munch is Best Described as a Entertainment. Please Like and Share the page for all Latest Bollywood Updates. Thanks for you support and love.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQasC1VIbN1TamHrp/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQasC1VIbN1TamHrp/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 - The Truth Hurts - August 31, 2020 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E15</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/90-day-fianc-the-other-way-s02e14-the-truth-hurts-august-31-2020-90-da.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 - The Truth Hurts - August 31, 2020 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E15" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:31:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:31:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/90-day-fianc-the-other-way-s02e14-the-truth-hurts-august-31-2020-90-da</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/90-day-fianc-the-other-way-s02e14-the-truth-hurts-august-31-2020-90-da.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 - The Truth Hurts - August 31, 2020&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E15  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way  &lt;br /&gt;90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 - The Truth Hurts - August 31, 2020   90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E15 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way - S02E14 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way 90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQzeb1VJVqB9VDENG/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQzeb1VJVqB9VDENG/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Unfortunate that Delhi CM’s order for doubling COVID testing needed MHA approval: Satyendar Jain</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/unfortunate-that-delhi-cm-s-order-for-doubling-covid-testing-needed-mh.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unfortunate that Delhi CM’s order for doubling COVID testing needed MHA approval: Satyendar Jain" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:28:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:28:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/unfortunate-that-delhi-cm-s-order-for-doubling-covid-testing-needed-mh</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/unfortunate-that-delhi-cm-s-order-for-doubling-covid-testing-needed-mh.html">&lt;p&gt;While speaking to media in the national capital on August 28, Health Minister of Delhi, Satyendar Jain, spoke on doubling COVID-19 testing in Delhi.  &lt;br /&gt;He said, “Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal gave instructions to double the COVID-19 testing but due to pressure from the Home Ministry, officials were not doing so. I am happy that after my letter, Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA) has clarified and cleared it and I am hopeful that testing will be doubled soon.”  &lt;br /&gt;“Home Ministry should first see COVID-19 cases in Gujarat, UP and rest of India, then talk about managing Delhi. This is unfortunate that despite Delhi CM’s approval for doubling the testing, the order had to be cleared by MHA also,” Satyendar Jain added.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">While speaking to media in the national capital on August 28, Health Minister of Delhi, Satyendar Jain, spoke on doubling COVID-19 testing in Delhi. He said, “Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal gave instructions to double the COVID-19 testing but due to pressure from the Home Ministry, officials were not doing so. I am happy that after my letter, Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA) has clarified and cleared it and I am hopeful that testing will be doubled soon.” “Home Ministry should first see COVID-19 cases in Gujarat, UP and rest of India, then talk about managing Delhi. This is unfortunate that despite Delhi CM’s approval for doubling the testing, the order had to be cleared by MHA also,” Satyendar Jain added.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQaQ-1VIG7gJekmdi/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQaQ-1VIG7gJekmdi/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Covid-19: Entry into M’sia barred for travellers from India, Indonesia, Philippines</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/covid-19-entry-into-m-sia-barred-for-travellers-from-india-indonesia-p.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Covid-19: Entry into M’sia barred for travellers from India, Indonesia, Philippines" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:24:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:24:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/covid-19-entry-into-m-sia-barred-for-travellers-from-india-indonesia-p</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/covid-19-entry-into-m-sia-barred-for-travellers-from-india-indonesia-p.html">&lt;p&gt;Long-term pass holders from India, Indonesia and Philippines will not be allowed to enter Malaysia effective Sept 7, following a spike in Covid-19 cases in these countries.  &lt;br /&gt;Senior Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob said the affected citizens from the three countries include those holding permanent resident status, participants of Malaysia My Second Home, expatriates and professional visit pass holders, spouses of Malaysian citizens and students.  &lt;br /&gt;Read more at   &lt;br /&gt;WATCH MORE:   &lt;br /&gt;SUBSCRIBE:   &lt;br /&gt;LIKE:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Long-term pass holders from India, Indonesia and Philippines will not be allowed to enter Malaysia effective Sept 7, following a spike in Covid-19 cases in these countries. Senior Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob said the affected citizens from the three countries include those holding permanent resident status, participants of Malaysia My Second Home, expatriates and professional visit pass holders, spouses of Malaysian citizens and students. Read more at WATCH MORE: SUBSCRIBE: LIKE:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ-7F1VJXf0N88c4-/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ-7F1VJXf0N88c4-/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">China-பகீரங்க மறுப்பு..Ladakh-ல் எல்லையை கடக்கவே இல்லையாம் Oneindia Tamil</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/china-ladakh-oneindia-tamil.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="China-பகீரங்க மறுப்பு..Ladakh-ல் எல்லையை கடக்கவே இல்லையாம் Oneindia Tamil" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:23:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:23:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/china-ladakh-oneindia-tamil</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/china-ladakh-oneindia-tamil.html">&lt;p&gt;லடாக்கில் எல்லையை கடக்கவே இல்லை, எங்கும் அத்துமீறலை நிகழ்த்தவில்லை என்று சீனா மறுப்பு தெரிவித்துள்ளது.  &lt;br /&gt;China standoff with India: We didn’t cross LAC in Ladakh says PLA army.  &lt;br /&gt;#IndiaChinaBorder  &lt;br /&gt;#IndiaChinaFight&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">லடாக்கில் எல்லையை கடக்கவே இல்லை, எங்கும் அத்துமீறலை நிகழ்த்தவில்லை என்று சீனா மறுப்பு தெரிவித்துள்ளது. China standoff with India: We didn’t cross LAC in Ladakh says PLA army. #IndiaChinaBorder #IndiaChinaFight</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQtzQ1VJIO0tVgkJO/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQtzQ1VJIO0tVgkJO/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">WATCH: Nandita Das with father Jatin Das in candid conversation with Rajdeep Sardesai</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/watch-nandita-das-with-father-jatin-das-in-candid-conversation-with-ra.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WATCH: Nandita Das with father Jatin Das in candid conversation with Rajdeep Sardesai" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:22:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:22:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/watch-nandita-das-with-father-jatin-das-in-candid-conversation-with-ra</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/watch-nandita-das-with-father-jatin-das-in-candid-conversation-with-ra.html">&lt;p&gt;In this latest episode of India Today India Tomorrow, catch the father-daughter duo, actress Nandita Das and Jatin Das in a candid conversation with Rajdeep Sardesai. For more, watch the full video of this latest episode.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">In this latest episode of India Today India Tomorrow, catch the father-daughter duo, actress Nandita Das and Jatin Das in a candid conversation with Rajdeep Sardesai. For more, watch the full video of this latest episode.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQiVW1VIfdmgNCxeX/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQiVW1VIfdmgNCxeX/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Be The Light Trailer #1 (2020) Cara Santana, Tom Cavanagh Drama Movie HD</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/be-the-light-trailer-1-2020-cara-santana-tom-cavanagh-drama-movie-hd.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Be The Light Trailer #1 (2020) Cara Santana, Tom Cavanagh Drama Movie HD" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:19:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:19:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/be-the-light-trailer-1-2020-cara-santana-tom-cavanagh-drama-movie-hd</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/be-the-light-trailer-1-2020-cara-santana-tom-cavanagh-drama-movie-hd.html">&lt;p&gt;&quot;In Be The Light, Celina Padilla is a down &amp;amp; out girl who has been estranged from her father Ramon for 9 years. She discovers that he is dying from cancer and has a limited time to live. He’s also being stubborn about getting the proper treatment, which is very expensive. Celina decides to go home, repair their relationship and get him the treatment. Celina reconnects with her old friend Marvin, a former OG who is working hard at getting a second chance at life by doing some good for his community. Ramon helped Marvin when he needed it most, and so Marvin wants to return the favor. Together, they decide to raise money for Ramon’s cancer treatment. When a music competition called THE GOLD STANDARD is announced with the grand prize being 500k, Celina pushes herself to write music and sing again. Armed with Celina’s songs they form a singing and dancing group called The Mysfit Toys in hopes of winning the prize to save Ramon.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">&quot;In Be The Light, Celina Padilla is a down &amp;amp; out girl who has been estranged from her father Ramon for 9 years. She discovers that he is dying from cancer and has a limited time to live. He’s also being stubborn about getting the proper treatment, which is very expensive. Celina decides to go home, repair their relationship and get him the treatment. Celina reconnects with her old friend Marvin, a former OG who is working hard at getting a second chance at life by doing some good for his community. Ramon helped Marvin when he needed it most, and so Marvin wants to return the favor. Together, they decide to raise money for Ramon’s cancer treatment. When a music competition called THE GOLD STANDARD is announced with the grand prize being 500k, Celina pushes herself to write music and sing again. Armed with Celina’s songs they form a singing and dancing group called The Mysfit Toys in hopes of winning the prize to save Ramon.&quot;</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQQtJ1VHyUhwNbfDb/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQQtJ1VHyUhwNbfDb/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/seorang-anak-bermain-di-samping-mural-bertema-covid-19-di-jakarta.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta." />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:19:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:19:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/seorang-anak-bermain-di-samping-mural-bertema-covid-19-di-jakarta</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/seorang-anak-bermain-di-samping-mural-bertema-covid-19-di-jakarta.html">&lt;p&gt;Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta. Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta. Seorang anak bermain di samping mural bertema Covid-19 di Jakarta.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQVV61VI1UhKDdNbF/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQVV61VI1UhKDdNbF/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Why Is Biden’s Lead Slipping?</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/why-is-biden-s-lead-slipping.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Is Biden’s Lead Slipping?" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:17:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:17:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/why-is-biden-s-lead-slipping</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/why-is-biden-s-lead-slipping.html">&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden’s poll numbers are slipping.  &lt;br /&gt;The former Vice President is currently leading Pres. Donald Trump in the polls.  &lt;br /&gt;He led by double digits over the summer.  &lt;br /&gt;Now, his lead has dropped to low single digits - in some polls Trump is within the margin of error.  &lt;br /&gt;In Wisconsin Biden is up by 3.5 points in the RealClearPolitics average.  &lt;br /&gt;At this time in 2016 Hillary Clinton led Trump by 11.5 points.  &lt;br /&gt;In the middle of a pandemic, economic collapse caused by the lockdowns, and racial strife Joe Biden is under performing.  &lt;br /&gt;According to polling traditionally Democratic Minnesota Trump and Biden are virtually tied.  &lt;br /&gt;The NY Post says the political analysts are puzzled as to why Biden’s lead is drastically falling.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Joe Biden’s poll numbers are slipping. The former Vice President is currently leading Pres. Donald Trump in the polls. He led by double digits over the summer. Now, his lead has dropped to low single digits - in some polls Trump is within the margin of error. In Wisconsin Biden is up by 3.5 points in the RealClearPolitics average. At this time in 2016 Hillary Clinton led Trump by 11.5 points. In the middle of a pandemic, economic collapse caused by the lockdowns, and racial strife Joe Biden is under performing. According to polling traditionally Democratic Minnesota Trump and Biden are virtually tied. The NY Post says the political analysts are puzzled as to why Biden’s lead is drastically falling.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQx3u1VJP_8fe2VeL/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQx3u1VJP_8fe2VeL/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Menengok Proses Uji Kompetensi Untuk Sopir Truk Di Surabaya</title>
  <link href="https://houtube.eu.org/menengok-proses-uji-kompetensi-untuk-sopir-truk-di-surabaya.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Menengok Proses Uji Kompetensi Untuk Sopir Truk Di Surabaya" />
  <published>2020-09-01T15:15:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-09-01T15:15:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://houtube.eu.org/menengok-proses-uji-kompetensi-untuk-sopir-truk-di-surabaya</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://houtube.eu.org/menengok-proses-uji-kompetensi-untuk-sopir-truk-di-surabaya.html">&lt;p&gt;Surabaya, KompasTV Jawa Timur. - Ribuan sopir truk/kontainer yang bernaung di keanggotaan Organisasi Angkutan Darat atau Organda khusus angkutan Tanjung Perak, Surabaya, mengikuti ujian sertifikasi.   &lt;br /&gt;Ujian sertifikasi ini, bertujuan untuk mengurangi resiko angka kecelakaan sopir truk kontainer.   &lt;br /&gt;Ujian diberikan langsung Badan Nasional Sertifikasi profesi  kepada para sopir truk melalui skema keahlian khusus.   &lt;br /&gt;Uji kompetensi ini wajib dilaksanakan sesuai amanat UU Ketenagakerjaan dan Keputusan Menteri Perhubungan.   &lt;br /&gt;Dalam uji kompetensi sertifikasi sopir truk ini, peserta harus memenuhi 3 hal yaitu: Knowledge atau pengetahuan, Skill atau kemampuan keahlian dan attitude atau sikap.   &lt;br /&gt;Melalui proses sertifikasi kompetensi ini, para sopir dibekali kemampuan mengemudikan truk kontainer yang ditandai dengan pemberian sertifikat kelayakan dari BNSP.   &lt;br /&gt;#Surabaya #Jatim #Sopir #Truk #Kontainer #Organda #Tanjung #Perak   &lt;br /&gt;MEDIA SOSIAL KOMPAS TV JAWA TIMUR :   &lt;br /&gt;facebook :    &lt;br /&gt;instagram :    &lt;br /&gt;twitter :     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://houtube.eu.org</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Surabaya, KompasTV Jawa Timur. - Ribuan sopir truk/kontainer yang bernaung di keanggotaan Organisasi Angkutan Darat atau Organda khusus angkutan Tanjung Perak, Surabaya, mengikuti ujian sertifikasi. Ujian sertifikasi ini, bertujuan untuk mengurangi resiko angka kecelakaan sopir truk kontainer. Ujian diberikan langsung Badan Nasional Sertifikasi profesi kepada para sopir truk melalui skema keahlian khusus. Uji kompetensi ini wajib dilaksanakan sesuai amanat UU Ketenagakerjaan dan Keputusan Menteri Perhubungan. Dalam uji kompetensi sertifikasi sopir truk ini, peserta harus memenuhi 3 hal yaitu: Knowledge atau pengetahuan, Skill atau kemampuan keahlian dan attitude atau sikap. Melalui proses sertifikasi kompetensi ini, para sopir dibekali kemampuan mengemudikan truk kontainer yang ditandai dengan pemberian sertifikat kelayakan dari BNSP. #Surabaya #Jatim #Sopir #Truk #Kontainer #Organda #Tanjung #Perak MEDIA SOSIAL KOMPAS TV JAWA TIMUR : facebook : instagram : twitter :</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQBxd1VJXVxsvzTuo/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQBxd1VJXVxsvzTuo/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>